Skip navigation

* Why Cryptohopper
    
    * EASY
    * PROFESSIONAL
    * MORE
        [Trading TerminalManage your complete portfolio from one place](https://www.cryptohopper.com/features/trading-terminal "Trading Terminal")[ExchangesConnect the world's top exchanges](https://www.cryptohopper.com/exchanges "Exchanges")[TournamentsShow your skills and win prizes with trading](https://www.cryptohopper.com/features/tournaments "Tournaments")[All featuresAn overview of these features and more](https://www.cryptohopper.com/features/all-features/trading-options "All features")
    
* Solutions

* Learn

* Company

Cryptohopper Privacy Policy: Our Commitment to Protecting Your Data
===================================================================

Last Updated: 21 January 2020

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Cryptohopper collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.Cryptohopper.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Cryptohopper.

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, register on the siteplace an orderfill out a formsubscribe to the newsletter and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.

We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information

Cryptohopper collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

* To improve customer service
    
* Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
    
* To personalize user experience We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
    
* To improve our Site We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
    
* To process transactions We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order.
    
* We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
    
* To send periodic emails

The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

Advertising

Ads appearing on our Site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Changes to this privacy policy

Cryptohopper has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Delete your data

You can deactivate your account and delete your data by going to your [user profile](https://www.cryptohopper.com/edit-profile), click on the Settings tab, and select "Deactivate your account".

* We will only retain your user data for 30 days and then it will be permanently deleted. You can reactivate your account at any point within 30 days of deactivation by logging back in.
    
* All your hoppers, subscriptions, templates, strategies, and other data will be deleted.
    
* You don't need to deactivate your account to change your username or to change your email address.
    
* If you want to use this username or email on another account, then you will need to change it in this account first, before deactivating this account.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at: Cryptohopper.com Johan van Hasseltweg 18a 1022 WV Amsterdam The Netherlands Tel: +31858769694 Mail: [\[email protected\]](https://www.cryptohopper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

[

](https://apps.apple.com/app/cryptohopper-crypto-trading/id1463052050)[

](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.cryptohopper_mobile)

Follow us on social media

EN

[

EN](https://www.cryptohopper.com/privacy " Switch to English language")[

NL](https://www.cryptohopper.com/nl/privacy " Switch to Dutch language")[

CZ](https://www.cryptohopper.com/cs/privacy " Switch to Czech language")[

DE](https://www.cryptohopper.com/de/privacy " Switch to German language")[

ES](https://www.cryptohopper.com/es/privacy " Switch to Spanish language")[

FR](https://www.cryptohopper.com/fr/privacy " Switch to French language")[

ID](https://www.cryptohopper.com/id/privacy " Switch to Indonesian language")[

JP](https://www.cryptohopper.com/ja/privacy " Switch to Japanese language")[

KO](https://www.cryptohopper.com/ko/privacy " Switch to Korean language")[

PL](https://www.cryptohopper.com/pl/privacy " Switch to Polish language")[

BR](https://www.cryptohopper.com/pt-br/privacy " Switch to Portuguese(Brazil) language")[

RU](https://www.cryptohopper.com/ru/privacy " Switch to Russian language")[

TR](https://www.cryptohopper.com/tr/privacy " Switch to Turkish language")[

ZH](https://www.cryptohopper.com/zh-cn/privacy " Switch to Chinese (Simplified) language")

Features

* [Algorithm Intelligence (AI)](https://www.cryptohopper.com/features/algorithm-intelligence "Algorithm Intelligence (AI)")

Resources

Company

Links

Disclaimer: Cryptohopper is not a regulated entity. Cryptocurrency bot trading involves substantial risks, and past performance is not indicative of future results. The profits shown in product screenshots are for illustrative purposes and may be exaggerated. Only engage in bot trading if you possess sufficient knowledge or seek guidance from a qualified financial advisor. Under no circumstances shall Cryptohopper accept any liability to any person or entity for (a) any loss or damage, in whole or in part, caused by, arising out of, or in connection with transactions involving our software or (b) any direct, indirect, special, consequential, or incidental damages. Please note that the content available on the Cryptohopper social trading platform is generated by members of the Cryptohopper community and does not constitute advice or recommendations from Cryptohopper or on its behalf. Profits shown on the Markteplace are not indicative of future results. By using Cryptohopper's services, you acknowledge and accept the inherent risks involved in cryptocurrency trading and agree to hold Cryptohopper harmless from any liabilities or losses incurred. It is essential to review and understand our Terms of Service and Risk Disclosure Policy before using our software or engaging in any trading activities. Please consult legal and financial professionals for personalized advice based on your specific circumstances.

©2017 - 2024 Copyright by Cryptohopper™ - All rights reserved.

Signed out
----------

For your safety, you are automatically signed out due to inactivity. Please sign in again to continue.

Ok
